Let's understand from Gaurang. Gaurang, throughout this
year, there are good view reports on insurance rates from many broking firms on
insurance counters. It is
also being said in the budget
that perhaps some more
announcements may come for the BPL category, soft category, on
insurance basis and you
can also choose LIC in this.
What are your views on insurance rates at this time,
but for a long time and in fact, the
name of LIC that you mentioned,
we had given our opinion on the IPO as well and the
IPO was above Rs 900, and even
today,
I think it is below its IPO price. And for the rest of the life
insurance companies,
along with LIC, SBI Life, HDFC Life and ICC
Prudential, there is a buy opinion here and our
estimate and assessment says Priyanka that the
understanding of people has improved now,
after the pandemic, they are taking bigger short sums and are paying
bigger premiums for it. The return of
life insurance companies is
improving and in non-life general
insurance, ICICI  I like the name Lombard
and if you
invest in the insurance sector then give it one and a half to two years
if you want to make good profits
because this change will take time,
right not at all, things have
changed a lot, people's mindset has changed
and you like stock specific ice lobs,
thank you very much Gaurang for your time
and today we will go ahead and share all these insights with us,
reliance is seen happening once again, so for once, are
you digesting the move that was seen, the gains that were there,
what kind of action can be seen on LAS at this time,
LAS has shown quite good strength for the last three days, the
index has also put in
all its strength to move, the
stock is still holding a good support,
so you will see that it is
standing around the previous day's high, so
I have nothing to fear here at all,
consolidation of course
is quite natural because the stock had
shown so much momentum last week itself, so my opinion would be
that we should take it upwards.  Keep
trailing your stop loss, the next
immediate levels can be seen forming up to 2800